Long ago, Gold Roger,
the King of Pirates, obtained
everything the world had to offer,
and his dying roads drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
And thus a new age began.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Oh, I'm done playing
through with the waiting?
Either way, I'm feeling alive!
Look out below!
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
Raise your flag up high!
Hail a brand new dawn!
Blaze across the sky!
Time to journey on!
On your mark!
Camel of other things!
Well, on Earth, a legendary!
Hooray!
If you can show your breath,
Then we'll make some waves!
We run our daunted!
Ain't no beginners!
Cause if you want it,
Then you're a winner!
For we are on the cruise!
And freedom is the only rule!
Fearless night and day!
Cause that's just our way!
Find one piece!
I'll be the first!
I've heard it be so bad!
Just a good verse!
It's all this real!
It must be cause my hand's on a wheel!
I'm done playing, filled with the waiting!
In a world I'm feeling
alive, but I'll be loud!
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
We have come so far!
Gotta make it to the end!
Whatever danger we find,
no one ever left behind!
I've always got your back, my friend!
Sail on shoreward, keep marching forward!
Dreaming from the very
first day I'd make my name!
And don't you know that
dream hasn't changed!
I'm done playing through with the wave!
In every world I'm feeling alive!
Look out below!
Wake up, sunshine!
And here we go!
We go!
What's it doing?
It's sleeping! Look!
No one's not headed
toward the island anymore!
The princess is leading it away from us!
It won't crash into us after all!
Don't let it hurt you!
Where do you think you're going?
You know you can't run away, don't you?
There is no escape!
If I'm going to steer the
Noah clear of the bubble,
then I have to swim as
far out to sea as I can!
The bubble will surely break
if it takes any more damage.
But the main entrance is too far away.
No, wait!
I believe Luffy and his friends were
the last ones to leave the Ryugu Palace.
If that's the case, perhaps
the gateway is still open?
Oh no!
Isn't there some way to help
instead of just standing here?
What does Vendur Decken have
to gain from this anyway?
Leave our princess alone, you monster!
It's not Shirahushi's fault!
She doesn't deserve to die for this!
Barney's climbing out of the ship too?
That can't be good!
What if he attacks her again?
There's no one to protect her!
She can't fight him!
Thank you, filthy traitor.
Have you lost your damn mind?
This is far from over.
I can make use of that madman.
Keep your wits about you, Luffy.
Fishmen are far stronger
than humans in the water.
Do not forget that!
I can't throw Luffy
too hard or he'll break
through the bubble and
go flying out to sea.
So I'm going to have to
do it extra carefully,
with exactly the right
amount of force. Now, Sanji!
Army de l 'air assault!
Don't shoot!
Huh, this thing's pretty big.
I guess I'm between the bubbles now.
Wait, Horty's still under the bubble.
We can't stop this thing,
but if we could slow it down even just
a little, maybe she could get away.
Don't let it catch her!
Alright princess, we'll
try to slow it down!
You get somewhere safe!
Damn it!
It's too heavy!
Are they crazy?
My people!
Who came up with that plan?
No matter how hard they pull,
that ship will never move an edge.
Why don't I just put
you out of your misery?
Come on! Back off!
You worthless scum, you're the reason
humans look down on our entire race.
My kingdom has no place for
sentimental weaklings like you.
Do it, Heart!
We're sorry, your majesty, just swim away.
Hurry!
I was right!
The entrance to the palace is still open!
Just hang in there, buddy!
She made it up to the gate.
She's swimming out to sea.
The Noah's still on her tail.
You can do it princess.
It's going up.
I can't steer this thing!
Poor, feeble humans.
Must be inconvenient.
You all act so high and mighty
when you're safe on land.
But here in the water, you're not even
a match for the smallest fishman child.
A man is only as strong as he
is at his weakest, I'm afraid.
You might be powerful up on the
island, but you're in my territory now.
Shut up and fight me!
You don't listen very well, do you?
I hate to break it to you, but if
you're worried about Shirahoshi,
you're going to be long dead
before that ship hits her.
Shark Arrow!
How arrogant to think you
had a chance in the sea?
Perhaps you understand at last!
In the bitter end, you humans will finally
see that you're unfit to rule this world.
A lesson learned far too late, I'm afraid!
Truly such a miserable creature.
Now, prepare to rot in hell!
Too bad that kind gesture was in vain.
Because I'm not about to let you get away.
I almost forgot to ask, Shirahoshi!
How does freedom feel?
After ten years,
you're no longer protected by the cold
stone walls of the hardshell tower!
And now it's time for you to
bleed to death, my darling!
That is, unless you'd rather be crushed
by the massive weight of the NOAH!
But one teeny tiny little magic word can
spare you this dread fate, and that's YES!
Simply under that one word,
and your troubles will be over!
I'm deeply sorry, Sir Dekkan,
but I simply can't do that!
Why must you refuse to marry me?!
Because you're not my type!
How the hell are you?
You need to learn how to treat a
lady, or anybody for that matter.
Shirahoshi is our baby sister.
We will never let you lay
a hand on her, not ever.
You came to save me, and Ho
is here as well. Thank you.
Well, hello, brothers-in-law.
We are not your family.
Oh, brothers!
Some of our people attempted to
save me, but then they were...
Now's not the type of tears, Shirahoshi!
Oh, please don't get mad at me!
I said don't cry!
Focus, you two!
Father told us that we shouldn't let
any harm come to the Noah Solatino!
We have to find a way to get
it safely back to the sea
floor without letting it
hit anything along the way!
Look out!
Listen!
We need you to mumble your way around
the underwater mountains and dredges!
Hey, don't rock the boat, baby!
But there's so many
obstacles, where should I go?
Up there!
The path should be a lot clearer that way!
Alright, I'll go!
He won't get away from me, Vassola!
You will never escape, my love.
It's as hopeless as you trying to
escape the hot pursuit of the Noah.
I'll chase after you as long as
I have to, my beautiful bride.
Good thing you showed up. Thanks a lot.
But you got hurt pretty bad back there.
Are you okay?
My pain means nothing
when so many soldiers,
citizens, and royal family
members were attacked.
So you see, there simply isn't time
for me to sit back and lick my wounds.
Well, in that case, can I ask you a favor?
Forgive me, but there's
no time for that, either.
A furboat like them are supposed to be
the fastest swimmers in the whole world.
But with my new power, I can
swim circles around them.
Not again!
Now, Shark Slicer!
Hey, we need to get on
top of that ship, quick!
Something Jinbei told me.
But the ship's in a bubble,
so it should be okay.
That would make sense.
Deccan is weak to seawater, just like you.
Despite being a fish man, he
needs air to move around freely.
It'll be easier for me to fight there.
And I'm about ready to
kick the crap out of
Heart and that weirdo
who likes to throw stuff.
Besides, I promised we'd be
Hachi when we left the tower.
I'm supposed to make sure she's safe.
It seems we are of one mind.
And just like our father, your
sons will become noble warriors.
With all of our strength, we will protect
Shirahoshi in body and spirit alike.
I made the same promise.
Yet we allowed ourselves to be bested by a
scoundrel who draws his
power from some drug?
It seems I've failed to keep
my word to our late mother.
I also regret being
suspicious of you at first.
It's no big deal, let's head to the deck!
I've got business there too.
Please, come on, fire!
Goodness, if it isn't Horny Jones!
Say, whatever happened to Neptune?
Dead, maybe.
By the way, I'm using the Noah to
torture Shirahoshi as we speak.
A genius idea on my part.
Don't you think, brother?
It's not bad.
But I think I've got an even better idea.
Do you now?
Well, let's hear it!
Actually, it's better if I show you.
If you died, what would
become of this ship?
Well, Dekkan?
Heart, you've made a terrible mistake.
I just touched you with my left hand!
You turned your back on me!
As I recall, Deacon, you
started this yourself.
You know, to be honest,
I was a bit nervous when I first saw the
shadow of the Noah looming
over Fishman Island.
But after I thought about it, breaking the
bubble didn't seem like such a bad idea.
Fishman Island would be wiped out, but
we'd still have the Fishman District.
And if you die, here and now, then your
Markmark power will deactivate, right?
Then the ship will come crashing
down right onto that useless kingdom.
Then nothing will remain.
What I want most, right now,
is to take care of all those
meddlesome straw-hat pirates.
For good.
True I stand to lose well thousands,
but it'll be easy enough for me to pick
up all the human slaves I want later on?
Thousands will die, huh?
I like that.
Why don't we start with you?
What are you doing?
Stop it!
Die for new Fishman Island.
We'll be sure to remember you.
You'll be dead before long,
and then the great ship
Noah will begin its descent,
bringing my wrath upon this wretched land.
You know, I'm a kind man, so just for you,
maybe I should make your
beloved join you in death.
Your time has come, princess.
He stabbed him!
First they're pals, now they're
shigging each other off!
No time to worry about that
now! Look out! Here he comes!
We'll stop you, Arnie!
Oh yeah, not likely.
You're not the ones I left.
Dear Brother Snow!
Run!
You have to get out of here right now!
What a pity.
You're kind to the world's fastest
swimmers, but with this power, I'm faster.
Help me!
GUN GUN FNAKESHAAAA!
Thank goodness!
I'm so glad you're here!
Brother!
And Straw Hat too?
That's right.
This time, we won't lose so easily.
Of course.
Meanwhile, at Fishman
Island's Conchcord Plaza...
Captain Vanderdecker doesn't like me
anymore, so he's left me here to die!
There's the brakes!
You're just one more thing I have to
sacrifice in my pursuit of Shilohoshi!
Quit crying and fight, you big baby!
Yeah, you're the only one figuring
out to beat up the Kraken!
I know you can win, Sodom!
Come on, take a spot!
But he's almost the
same size as the Kraken,
so I wonder why he's
so scared to fight him.
Well, I wouldn't want to.
There, there, perhaps you
didn't hear correctly.
He didn't say sacrifice.
He said, uh, some help would be nice.
Huh?
You didn't really think he would destroy
the island and leave you to your death,
did you?
But he did say I was gonna die!
He was just saying you should fight
as though you were prepared to die.
Really?
Tell him.
Uh, yeah! Totally!
He's lucky his captain trusts him with
something so important that's great!
What a big boy!
Uh, what he means is you're strong!
Oh!
Now I get it!
I don't think you do.
Anyway, this is for you.
I want you to take it so you can help us
defeat those mean old Straw Hats, okay?
That's an energy steroid! Wait a sec.
How's it gonna work on somebody that big?
What the? It works!
Extra well!
I'm sorry, Captain.
I should have trusted you all along.
Nice work.
That stupid squid is history now.
Hey, are you okay there, buddy? Oh, no.
He's unconscious.
Hey, boy. You do.
He's not even the same person anymore.
The captain will be so proud of me!
Who's next?
I think he said to kill that guy.
The blue dude?
Okay!
Jinbei!
Behind you!
Fishman Karate!
7,000 brick!
Roundhouse kick!
This is why I say kick!
What's the big deal?
Nami, there's a lady here.
Keep the butt shockwaves
to yourself, you creep.
That's it, Cal!
No! That hurt!
He just hit me!
Here's the deal!
If you put so much as a single
scratch on our beautiful map goddess,
then I'll put another gap in your team!
What?
Why are all his kicks working so well?
I don't know if this guy is crazy
strong, or the giant guy is crazy weak!
Oh, great!
Now I'm all dirty!
Whoa!
It wasn't my fault!
That guy knocked me over!
You want to fight?
Then fight me!
I want a piece of you
too, you big dumpling!
Okay, so leave us out of it!
Not again!
I don't know but I'm scared.
He's stronger than usual.
Get ready
He cut the net like paper
I don't get it.
He was writhing in pain, and
then he changed color. Yeah,
I don't get it either,
but that's exactly what happened
to Heart when he transformed.
At least Heart had the decency
not to swing so up at us.
Oh, this feels good.
So much energy.
Let's see.
Now, who should I butcher next?
Don't be shy!
What do we do now?
He's not going to quit
slashing until somebody...
Ah, come on, who's it going to be?
This is just way too many swords.
Hold on,
I'm calling dibs on you
might as well get a warm
-up before we go to the
new world should be fun
That sucks it's not as strong
underwater shit not as strong tough
luck look give it up already We're
thousands of meters underwater, you fool.
You can fight, but there's no
way in hell you're going to win.
Not against a fish man.
See?
Either way, the whole island is doomed.
That includes your friends, the
princess, and everyone else down there.
You're just a week late. Get it?
You can't protect anyone.
Watch me.
I'll save them all.
I trained for two years.
I'm ready.